<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour_Guide</string>
    <string name="map">MAP</string>
    <string name="visit">VISIT</string>
    <string name="oberhausen">Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="start">Start Tour</string>
    <string name="details">With around 211,000 inhabitants, Oberhausen is one of the medium-sized cities in the Ruhr Metropolis (Germany) . Shaped in the past by a great industrial tradition, the city initiated a successful structural change two decades ago and has since become a popular city travel destination. In particular, the \"New Center Oberhausen\" is considered a successful example of the gradual change of an entire region. With the CentrO, Europe\'s most modern shopping and leisure center, the city\'s 117-meter landmark, the Oberhausen gasometer, Stage Metronom Musicaltheater, Aquapark and the largest Sea Life Aquarium in Germany as well as many other visitor attractions, the \"Neue Mitte\" attracts more than a year 23 million guests in the Ruhr Metropolis.</string>
    <string name="category_events">Event</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotel</string>
    <string name="category_places">Place</string>
    <string name="spots">Oberhausen Spots</string>
    <string name="centro">Centro</string>
    <string name="centro_desc">CentrO is a shopping mall in Oberhausen, North Rhine-Westphalia, Germany. It forms part of a large commercial development called the Neue Mitte. CentrO is Germany\'s largest shopping mall.</string>
    <string name="centro_opening">Everyday from 10AM-8PM except Sunday </string>
    <string name="centro_adress">Centroallee 1000, 46047 Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="gasometer">Gasometer</string>
    <string name="gasometer_desc">The Gasometer Oberhausen is a former gas holder in Oberhausen, Germany, which has been converted into an exhibition space. It has hosted several large scale exhibitions, including two by Christo and Jeanne-Claude</string>
    <string name="gasometer_opening">Everday from 10AM-6PM</string>
    <string name="gaseometer_adress">Arenastraße 11, 46047 Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="ludwig">LUDWIGGALERIE Oberhausen Castle</string>
    <string name="ludwig_desc"><![CDATA[Global art collection in a palace, featuring ancient & contemporary works, with regular exhibitions.]]></string>
    <string name="ludwig_opening">Everday from 11AM-6PM except Monday</string>
    <string name="ludwig_adress">Konrad-Adenauer-Allee 46, 46049 Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="desc">desc</string>
    <string name="time">time</string>
    <string name="flag">flag</string>
    <string name="owners">Owners</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="Owner">Owner: \ </string>
    <string name="addressdisplay">Adress:  \ </string>
    <string name="opening">Opening time: \ </string>
    <string name="opening_date">Opening date: \ </string>
    <string name="centro_time">12 September 1996</string>
    <string name="gasometer_time">27 February 1927</string>
    <string name="ludwig_time">1998</string>
    <string name="shortfilm">International Short Film Festival</string>
    <string name="shortfilm_desc">The International Short Film Festival Oberhausen, founded in 1954, is one of the oldest short film festivals in the world. Held in Oberhausen, it is one of the major international platforms for short form.</string>
    <string name="shortfilm_adress">Elsässer Str. 26, 46045 Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="shortfilm_time">Every Year \nEarly May</string>
    <string name="ruhr">Ruhr-in-Love</string>
    <string name="ruhr_desc">Ruhr in Love or Ruhr-in-Love is an annual family festival of the electronic music scene in Oberhausen, Germany, where it has been held since June 2003.</string>
    <string name="ruhr_time">Every Year \nJune or July</string>
    <string name="ruhr_adress">Olga-Park, Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="kirmes">Sterkrade Fronleichnamkirmes</string>
    <string name="kirmes_desc">The Sterkrader Fronleichnamskirmes is a street and folk festival, which takes place in the city center of the Oberhausen district Sterkrade. In recent years, the fair called the biggest street fair in Europe; however, the available space has been increasingly limited by various construction projects in recent years. The number of visitors is one million people.</string>
    <string name="kirmes_time">Every Year \n30 May - 04 June</string>
    <string name="kirmes_adress">Bahnhofstraße 19, 46145 Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="piwy">Piwy\'s Burger</string>
    <string name="piwy_desc">Agreat restaurant with great burgers and delicious homemade sauces</string>
    <string name="piwy_opening">Monday-Tuesday, Thursday-Friday 4AM-10PM \nWednesday 12AM-10PM \nSaturday-Sunday 1AM-10PM</string>
    <string name="piwy_owner">Pierre Wroblewski</string>
    <string name="piwy_adress">189 Weierstraße, 46149 Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="shalimar">SHALIMAR</string>
    <string name="shalimar_desc">Indian restaurant with a variety of exotic dishes</string>
    <string name="shalimar_opening"><![CDATA[Monday-Friday 12-3PM & 5-10PM \\nSatuday-Sunday 1PM-11PM]]></string>
    <string name="shalimar_owner">Rizwan Khan</string>
    <string name="shalimar_adress">Buschhausener Str. 58, 46049 Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="tryp">Tryp Centro Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="tryp_desc">Set. 2.1 km from Oberhausen-Osterfeld Süd train station, this contemporary hotel is also a 3-minute walk from Gasometer Oberhausen, a former gas storage facility converted into an exhibition space, and 33 km from Düsseldorf International Airport.  The relaxed rooms provide free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs, desks and minibars. Upgraded rooms offer tea and coffeemakers, and suites add sitting areas.</string>
    <string name="tryp_adress">Centroallee 280, 46047 Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="tryp_opening">24 hours</string>
    <string name="nh">Hotel NH Oberhausen</string>
    <string name="nh_desc">Set 1.2 km from Oberhausen railway station, this modern hotel is also 7 km from Zoo-Duisburg and 9 km from Duisburg\'s inner harbor.   The contemporary rooms feature free Wi-Fi and flat-screen TVs, plus work desks, chairs and minibars.</string>
    <string name="nh_opening">24 hours</string>
    <string name="nh_adress">Düppelstraße 2, 46045 Oberhausen</string>
</resources>